<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Boring Posts on Trenton Broughton</title>
    <link>http://devd.io:8001/tags/boring-posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Boring Posts on Trenton Broughton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 09:03:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://devd.io:8001/tags/boring-posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple OS X XKCD client with Automator</title>
      <link>http://devd.io:8001/posts/2014-05-20-09-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 09:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devd.io:8001/posts/2014-05-20-09-03/</guid>
      <description>I am a big fan of the xkcd comics, and was toying with different ways to view the current comic directly. At one point, I built a complicated flow to put the current comic on my desktop using Geek Tool, but I wanted something I could just open periodically. Finally, I decided to give Automator a try. Turns out, it&amp;rsquo;s incredibly simple.
Here is my final flow:
Simple enough! You can find those two actions under the Internet section in the Library:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handy Sale Advertisement Guide.</title>
      <link>http://devd.io:8001/posts/2013-12-02-12-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 12:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devd.io:8001/posts/2013-12-02-12-47/</guid>
      <description>In this holiday season (and pretty much any other time, now) it is nearly impossible to avoid the bombardment of advertisements. Maybe i&amp;rsquo;ve been growing cynical, but i have become a lot more antagonistic toward companies that advertise in ways i don&amp;rsquo;t like. So here is the handy guide i use to interpret ads.
 Sign says: &amp;ldquo;Deals starting at just $20!&amp;rdquo;
i read: &amp;ldquo;Absolutely nothing under $20&amp;rdquo;
 Sign says: &amp;ldquo;Save at up to $10!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New day, new attempt</title>
      <link>http://devd.io:8001/posts/2013-11-16-00-58/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2013 00:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devd.io:8001/posts/2013-11-16-00-58/</guid>
      <description>Just finished a little work with liquidluck. i hadn&amp;rsquo;t heard of it before, but zigg mentioned it, so i thought i would give it a try. Honestly, i wasn&amp;rsquo;t really sure about yet another static site generator, but so far i am impressed. Now if only i can keep writing things down.
i will also hopefully get the template i made for it packaged up. i&amp;rsquo;m not completely satisfied with it, but it will keep me going for the time being.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>