<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hugo on Trenton Broughton</title>
    <link>https://ikso.us/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hugo on Trenton Broughton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 17:58:01 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ikso.us/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Hugo Site Deployments With CircleCI</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/automatic-hugo-deployments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 17:58:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/automatic-hugo-deployments/</guid>
      <description>Generating static sites with Hugo is easy enough, but I wanted something a little more automated. I also wanted to deploy my site to Github Pages from another computer (or even my phone) without needing to run the hugo command locally and pushing the generated code back to Github. If you are unfamiliar with Github Pages, check out the introduction.
Prep Work &amp;ndash; Getting Things Set Up CircleCI uses Docker containers to run CI jobs, so I knew that I would need a Hugo image to build my site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating From Blogger</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/migrating-from-blogger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:44:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/migrating-from-blogger/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I suddenly remembered that I had written several posts on Blogger and forgotten all about them. I decided to migrate the content over to Hugo and take advantage of Google&amp;rsquo;s Takeout program.
I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really sure what I would get when exporting a blog, but I was not thrilled when I downloaded my content. Instead of a directory of HTML files, I received a single ATOM feed of all of my posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And now, Hugo!</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 21:41:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/hugo/</guid>
      <description>After forgetting about this for, hmm, three years, I figured it was time to start writing again. And of course, I can&amp;rsquo;t just write. I also have to start over with everything. So this time around I am using Hugo for my static site engine.
I enjoy using Hugo as it has some nice tricks up its sleeve while being quite easy to get running.
Recently, I have also been using VSCode, and to make it a little easier to generate posts I use the following launch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
