<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>go on Trenton Broughton</title>
    <link>https://ikso.us/tags/go/</link>
    <description>Recent content in go on Trenton Broughton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 02:34:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ikso.us/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unmarshalling a timestamp to time.Time from JSON in go</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/unmarshal-timestamp-as-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 02:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/unmarshal-timestamp-as-time/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes when working with remote APIs, you will come across dates formatted as Unix timestamps (an integer number of seconds since the epoch1). Go has a very nice native type for dealing with times, though, and it would be nice to be able to directly unmarshal2 to that type without doing the type conversions later. Fortunately, we can do easily do this by overriding the UnmarshalJSON method.
To do this, we will create a custom type that embeds time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go For a Loop</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/go-for-a-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:48:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/go-for-a-loop/</guid>
      <description>Go, like many languages, has a for loop. The snippet below can help to understand the versatility of these loops. This mechanism goes well beyond simply counting integers, but can be used to implement any number of looping patterns. The important thing to remember is that the second expression in the for loop definition controls the loop, and can be used with any function or method that returns a bool, or any expression that evaluates to a bool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And now, Hugo!</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 21:41:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/hugo/</guid>
      <description>After forgetting about this for, hmm, three years, I figured it was time to start writing again. And of course, I can&amp;rsquo;t just write. I also have to start over with everything. So this time around I am using Hugo for my static site engine.
I enjoy using Hugo as it has some nice tricks up its sleeve while being quite easy to get running.
Recently, I have also been using VSCode, and to make it a little easier to generate posts I use the following launch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
