<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blahg Posts on Trenton Broughton</title>
    <link>https://ikso.us/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blahg Posts on Trenton Broughton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 23:08:11 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ikso.us/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Need a Kubernetes Upgrade Path</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/why-you-need-an-upgrade-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 09:07:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/why-you-need-an-upgrade-path/</guid>
      <description>The recent Kubernetes vulnerability CVE-2018-1002105 should be a wake up call to any organization that is running Kubernetes, but does not have a regular update strategy in place. I won&amp;rsquo;t go into detail about the vulnerability as that is well documented in many places, but what I want to focus on is the challenge of keeping your cluster up to date.
Keeping up with Kubernetes releases can certainly be challenging as it is a fairly fast moving project, and it is also somewhat complex to deploy especially on bare metal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 21:39:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Trenton. I am an explorer seeking to understand the world around me. I write code, manage servers, and automate the mundane to allow people the time to let their creativity shine.
I love to read &amp;ndash; especially in cozy coffee shops, and I love walking down a road I have never travelled. Most of all, I enjoy the time I am able to spend with my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating From Blogger</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/migrating-from-blogger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:44:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/migrating-from-blogger/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I suddenly remembered that I had written several posts on Blogger and forgotten all about them. I decided to migrate the content over to Hugo and take advantage of Google&amp;rsquo;s Takeout program.
I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really sure what I would get when exporting a blog, but I was not thrilled when I downloaded my content. Instead of a directory of HTML files, I received a single ATOM feed of all of my posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And now, Hugo!</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 21:41:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/hugo/</guid>
      <description>After forgetting about this for, hmm, three years, I figured it was time to start writing again. And of course, I can&amp;rsquo;t just write. I also have to start over with everything. So this time around I am using Hugo for my static site engine.
I enjoy using Hugo as it has some nice tricks up its sleeve while being quite easy to get running.
Recently, I have also been using VSCode, and to make it a little easier to generate posts I use the following launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple OS X XKCD client with Automator</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/2014-05-20-09-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 09:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/2014-05-20-09-03/</guid>
      <description>I am a big fan of the xkcd comics, and was toying with different ways to view the current comic directly. At one point, I built a complicated flow to put the current comic on my desktop using Geek Tool, but I wanted something I could just open periodically. Finally, I decided to give Automator a try. Turns out, it&amp;rsquo;s incredibly simple.
Here is my final flow:
Simple enough! You can find those two actions under the Internet section in the Library:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attaching StringIO Data to a Mailgun Message</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-12-19-22-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 22:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-12-19-22-48/</guid>
      <description>Recently i started using Mailgun for our outgoing messages. They have a very nice API, and take a lot of the heavy lifting out of creating multipart messages.
If you are using requests (or treq) to send the messages through their REST API, however, you may have noticed that you must specify &amp;ldquo;attachment&amp;rdquo; as the key, and an open file handle as the value. This works great if you are sending files from the filesystem, but if you need to send generated or in memory data as a file attachment, it just doesn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Picture is worth how many words? Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-12-05-13-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 13:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-12-05-13-01/</guid>
      <description>i was playing around with some imaging code, and started wondering what it would look like to create some images out of text. i have worked with stenography in the past, but this time i didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hide the text, i wanted to pack the image with it.
First things first, i need some text. Time to turn to trusty Project Gutenberg. i will be using the text of Moby Dick for this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handy Sale Advertisement Guide.</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-12-02-12-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 12:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-12-02-12-47/</guid>
      <description>In this holiday season (and pretty much any other time, now) it is nearly impossible to avoid the bombardment of advertisements. Maybe i&amp;rsquo;ve been growing cynical, but i have become a lot more antagonistic toward companies that advertise in ways i don&amp;rsquo;t like. So here is the handy guide i use to interpret ads.
 Sign says: &amp;ldquo;Deals starting at just $20!&amp;rdquo;
i read: &amp;ldquo;Absolutely nothing under $20&amp;rdquo;
 Sign says: &amp;ldquo;Save at up to $10!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday.</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-11-29-15-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 15:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-11-29-15-12/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday means something quite different to me. See, three years ago on Black Friday, i was mugged. Not a &amp;ldquo;Hey you, give me your wallet&amp;rdquo; kind of mugging, but more of the &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll just smash your face and not ask&amp;rdquo; kind. i woke up in the hospital without any memory of what happened (in fact, i lost several hours worth of memories). i went through two surgeries, and had my jaw wired shut for a couple of months, but it could have been a lot worse &amp;ndash; especially for my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Uploaded</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-11-18-09-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 09:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-11-18-09-34/</guid>
      <description>I whipped up this theme for liquidluck recently. It is based on Bootstrap 3, and doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain many bells or whistles (as you can see).
Clone it here https://github.com/trenton42/liquidluck-theme-bootstrap3
i will (hopefully) be working on some improvements in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New day, new attempt</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-11-16-00-58/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2013 00:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/2013-11-16-00-58/</guid>
      <description>Just finished a little work with liquidluck. i hadn&amp;rsquo;t heard of it before, but zigg mentioned it, so i thought i would give it a try. Honestly, i wasn&amp;rsquo;t really sure about yet another static site generator, but so far i am impressed. Now if only i can keep writing things down.
i will also hopefully get the template i made for it packaged up. i&amp;rsquo;m not completely satisfied with it, but it will keep me going for the time being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All of Your Friends are Doing it!</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/all-of-your-friends-are-doing-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/all-of-your-friends-are-doing-it/</guid>
      <description>All Your Data Are Belong to Us Recently I was browsing LinkedIn when I saw this banner:    Grow your network!!!   Then, the next day they send me an email:      34 people now? Are you just making up these numbers?  It seems they really, really want me to give up my address book. They even call out my friends who have already done this, implying that my unfortunate pals endorse this sort of behaviour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to buy me a birthday card</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/how-to-buy-me-birthday-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/how-to-buy-me-birthday-card/</guid>
      <description>Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m just overly pragmatic, but this sums up how I feel about getting birthday cards:
  I especially remember thinking about this while lying in the hospital recovering from surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac OS X: When Trackpad Gestures Stop Working</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/mac-os-x-when-trackpad-gestures-stop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/mac-os-x-when-trackpad-gestures-stop/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I have been having problems with trackpad gestures suddenly failing to work, as well as the keyboard shortcuts for switching between full screen apps and spaces (normally, pressing ^L or ^R would switch to the next space or full screen app, but when it stopped working, it would skip full screen apps). I had been searching for a solution for a couple of days, and had previously been resorting to restarting my laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Urban Life, Culture, and Startups</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/rethinking-urban-life-culture-and/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/rethinking-urban-life-culture-and/</guid>
      <description>Not so long ago, we had a dream. The dream went a little like this: 2.4 children, a dog, a cat, a house in the suburbs and a 9-5 job at that big,&amp;nbsp;faceless&amp;nbsp;company in the city. Who knows what they did at that company, but as long as we kept pushing the blue button after the yellow button, we knew that when we reached 65 years and 1 day old, we would have that nice pension that would take care of us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Contribution Necessary?</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/no-contribution-necessary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/no-contribution-necessary/</guid>
      <description>I saw the Dinner With Barack contest today, and thought I would take a look at it. At first, it looked like the only way to enter was to make a campaign contribution, but that did not sound right. I looked a little more closely and saw that there was a link to enter without donating.
  Highlighted: Contributing will not improve chances of winning.  So I signed up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5x5 Night: Firing Up Local Entrepreneurship</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/5x5-night-firing-up-local/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 22:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/5x5-night-firing-up-local/</guid>
      <description>In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of it yet, 5x5 Night is a monthly event in Grand Rapids, Michigan that encourages anyone to come up with an idea for a chance to win a $5,000 prize. The ideas can be anything, but must include a plan that outlines the next step that will be taken if it is chosen.   I am very excited about tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s event, and would like to give my own analysis of the five ideas that will be presented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ghost Writer is... Invisible</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/ghost-writer-is-invisible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/ghost-writer-is-invisible/</guid>
      <description>Wait, Blogging Needs Words? So I had this plan to become a famous blogger. I could really see it: Blog posts everyday! Amazing information! So I did what I needed to do. I sat down and started writing. Here is what I came up with:
  Some of my greatest work  Ok, I was not prepared for this. I actually have to write stuff? I need ideas? Maybe I should have seen this coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Crusher Complex or How I learned to stop Sheldoning and start loving the Wil</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/crusher-complex-or-how-i-learned-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/crusher-complex-or-how-i-learned-to/</guid>
      <description>I had a Sheldon moment. It happened over twenty years ago, but I just realized what actually happened while watching an episode of The Big Bang Theory. In this episode, Sheldon tells of how he traveled eleven hours by bus to meet Wil Wheaton at a Star Trek convention, only to be disappointed by the star&amp;rsquo;s absence. Wil then becomes number six on Sheldon&amp;rsquo;s arch enemy list.
Wil was also on my arch enemy list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping the &#43; in Google&#43;</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/keeping-in-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/keeping-in-google/</guid>
      <description>Reading posts on the Internet can be a very depressing thing. I do not quite know what it is, but there is something about the Internet that can bring out the worst in people. If you have not experienced this first hand, all you need to do is post something you like about the presidential candidate you support on a web page somewhere. I can almost guarantee that before too long, someone will come along and tell you that you are an idiot and that you should shut up (but probably in a much less polite tone than I will post here).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two tips for faster email reading in Gmail: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/two-tips-for-faster-email-reading-in_27/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/two-tips-for-faster-email-reading-in_27/</guid>
      <description>Two tips for faster email reading in Gmail: Part 2
 If you are anything like me, most of your communication happens through email. This can be a time consuming task, so I am always looking for ways to make things more efficient. In this post, I am going to outline two of the things that I use to spend a little less time dealing with email and a little more time getting things done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two tips for faster email reading in Gmail: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://ikso.us/posts/two-tips-for-faster-email-reading-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 02:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ikso.us/posts/two-tips-for-faster-email-reading-in/</guid>
      <description>Two tips for faster email reading in Gmail: Part 1  If you are anything like me, most of your communication happens through email. This can be a time consuming task, so I am always looking for ways to make things more efficient. In this post, I am going to outline two of the things that I use to spend a little less time dealing with email and a little more time getting things done.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>